Antony Budianto

antonybudianto@gmail.com
antonybudianto.com
linkedin.com/in/antonybudianto
github.com/antonybudianto

Biodata



Name Antony Budianto

Gender Male

Place and Date of Birth Pontianak, August 8th, 1993

Language English (proficient), Indonesia (native)

Summary

A software engineer and open source contributor with 4+ years experience on software development, web design and development, git, writing unit and end-to-end tests, deployment and setup CI server. Actively contributing to open source and listed as one of the top 10 JavaScript GitHub developer in Indonesia by git-awards.com

Educations

September 2011 - March 2015 Binus University, Bachelor Degree, Information Systems major

Work experiences

September 2016 - present Senior Software Development Engineer at GDP Labs

Develop enterprise class HR platform as front-end engineer using Angular

September 2015 - August 2016 Software Development Engineer at GDP Labs

Develop enterprise applications using Angular JS, Angular 2.0, and Gulp

September 2014 - August 2015 Network Administrator at Binus University - Software Laboratory Center

Cloning images for software lab computers, ensure networks running well, patching, calibration,

maintenance, and develop various network-based applications

August 2013 - September 2014 Teaching Assistant at Binus University - Software Laboratory Center

Assists students in programming class, making cases, marking student assignments and learn many

hardskills and softskills

Certifications

May 2013 1st winner: HIMSISFO Competition 2013 "Infinite Creation" Web Design and Development

Competition

April 2015 5th rank: Research and Expo Competition (REOC) 2014. E-Learning Development for

Indonesian Traditional Music.

Skills

HTML, JS, CSS, React, React Native, Angular, NodeJS, Laravel, Jenkins, Docker

Portfolio



Tamar Gold Shop

Tamar Gold Shop is web development project that consists gold credit simulation, sell and buy gold, and more. This web is developed using Codelgniter. http://logammulia-dinar.com



Angular Attack 2016

Online 48-hours hackathon sponsored by Google https://starcoks.2016.angularattack.io



Tilt Master

A simple Android game where player only need to tilt their device, avoiding obstacles to the end. This is one of my project while I worked as Teaching Assistant. I also developed the parser to parse object created by AB 2D Studio.

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tiltmaster.res



Room Network Manager



AB 2D Game Studio



GitFun

https://gitfun-web.herokuapp.com/



GitFun Mobile

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.antonybudianto.gitfun